bsdmag.org 2019-11-27

# Privacy Policy - BSD MAG

This privacy policy sets out how Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. Komandytowa uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. komandytowa is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

## What we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like what information you are interested in, to more complex things like, recording your behavior and actions while using the site.

Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. Komandytowa also collects information on our users by your voluntary submissions and through cookie technology. When you use our services or view content provided by us, we automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or register to the Site, we collect certain information from you. We refer to this information as “Personal Information.”

**PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED VIA THE SITE**

If you are a user of our Service (a “ ** _Customer_** ”) or otherwise visit our Site, we collect the following type of information through your use of the Site:

  * **Contact, Account, and Billing Information:**  We process Personal Information that you provide through creation and management of your account, such as your name, e-mail address, payment and order information.
  * **Comments & Forum: **This website contains features that enable you to post reviews, comments or other content that is publicly viewable. You should be aware that any personal information you submit as part of those posts can be read, collected, or used by other visitors to the Website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to publicly post on the Website. If you choose to post a comment on our blog or forum, we require you to provide your name and your email address (we do not publish your email address). By posting a comment, you consent to our publication and storage of the information.An anonymized string created from your Email Address (also called a hash) is provided to the Gravatar service to see if a profile picture of you is available for display. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/> Prior to approval of your comment, your profile picture is only visible to administrators. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. Following approval of your comment, your comment text, your Name, and Website (URL) (if provided) are visible to the public. Your comment, including comment text, your Name, Email Address, Website (URL), IP Address and User Agent, is shared with the Akismet service to determine whether or not your comment is spam. The Akismet service privacy policy is available here:[ https://automattic.com/privacy/](https://automattic.com/privacy/) 
  * **Online Course:** If you choose to undertake a course using our Services, you give permission for processing and storage of any information provided by you related to the course progress (this includes: marks, exams, assigments, certificates).
  * **User ID and Password Information**  . We process Customers’ user ID and password information to enable them to log into and use the Service. We process this Personal Information only as necessary to provide the Service to you under our Terms of Service. In the event you are able to log into our Site or Service through a social networking site ( _e.g._ , Facebook or Twitter), we may receive Personal Information in accordance with the privacy policy of that site, which we may add to information you have already provided us.

## What we do with the information we gather

The information Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. komandytowa collects is used in a variety of ways: for internal review; to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; to notify you about updates; to provide you information you have requested; and to let you know about our products and services.

We use Personal Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Information you share

Our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes such as to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

## Information we share

Our policy is not to disclose personally identifiable information to unrelated third parties unless required to do so by law or legal process. Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. komandytowa, at its sole discretion, reserves the right to make exceptions to this policy in extraordinary circumstances on a case-by-case basis.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use **Intercom** as a analytics services tool that helps us drive Sales and provide Support to our users. Intercom helps us understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom’s use of cookies, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy>. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://protect-eu.mimecast.com/s/zMP6C0glXI29np7TOQGei?domain=intercom.com). Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms](https://protect-eu.mimecast.com/s/_s9hCg5BQCljvDoc7KDEG?domain=intercom.com). If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.

We also use **Google Analytics** to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We also use **Lucky Orange** analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience.

Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity.

Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system.

To view and manage data that Lucky Orange has collected about you on the LuckyOrange.com website, or to opt out of future tracking please visit data privacy management tool here : <https://privacy.luckyorange.com/>

**BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

[[

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

]]

## Your Controls and Choices

**Opt-Outs.**  We may provide you with the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personal information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. If you decide to opt-out, we may not be able to provide certain features of the Offerings to you.

**Communication Preferences.**  If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included on such communications or on the Offerings. Please note, however, that you may be unable to opt-out of certain service-related communications.

**Blocking Cookies.**  You can remove or block certain cookies using the settings in your browser but the Offerings may cease to function properly if you do so.

**Do Not Track Signals.**  Your Web browser may have a “do not track” setting which, when enabled, causes your browser to send a do not track HTTP header file or “signal” to each site you visit. Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

## No Children Under Age 13

The Offerings are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13, nor does Hakin9 Media sp. z o.o. sp. Komandytowa knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not attempt to register for the Offerings or send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we confirm that we have collected personal information from someone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information promptly. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 and believe that we might have any information from or about such child, please contact us at the email or mailing address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

## Your Rights

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Ilia@software.com.pl

or use the provided tools below:

1.Data rectification request form.

* * *

2.Click here to export your data : 

* * *

3.Click here to delete your data: 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

## Data Retention

When you place an order through the Site or use our Services, we will maintain your Personal Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

## Links to other Website

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Contact Us

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at ilia@software.com.pl
